嗨嗨
Hey.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.    - Hey.
我们来说再见 我们要去俄亥俄州
We're here to say goodbye. We're off to Ohio.
对 去收养中心面谈
Oh, right, your adoption interview.
没错 我们要和怀我们孩子的孕妇见面
Yep. We'll meet the lady who could be carrying our baby.
我不敢相信你们会抱着孩子回来 有够奇怪
I can't believe it. When you come back, you'll have a baby. That is so weird.
而且有够不正确
And so incorrect.
她只怀孕几个月
She's only a couple months pregnant.
她也许高兴有人申请 但不一定喜欢我们
She liked our application, who knows if she'll like us.
拜托 她会爱死你们
Oh, come on, she's gonna love you guys.
谢谢 但我们尽量不抱太大希望
Oh, thank you. But we're trying not to get our hopes up.
中途可能障碍重重
A lot could still get in our way.
她也许不接受申请 觉得别对夫妻比较好
She could decide against adoption, like another couple better.
宝宝要叫什么名字？
What are you gonna name it?
我可能会得到一种病 让人听不懂我说的话
I could develop a condition in which I talk and talk, and no one hears a word.
但想想看好吗？万一一切顺利呢？
But just think, okay? What if everything goes right?
万一这女人真的选你们？
What if this woman does pick you guys?
天啊 她一定会选我们
Oh, my God. She's gonna pick us!
所以我们仍坚持 "不抱太大希望"？
So we're standing firm on "not getting our hopes up"?
不 我知道可能出错 但顺利的话…
No. I know things could still go wrong, but if they don't...
我们就会有孩子了 孩子
...if this works out, we're gonna have a baby. A baby!
- 对 但是…   - 天啊 一定会成功
- Yes. But...    - Oh, my God. It's gonna work!
我们要让事情成功
We're gonna make it work!
我会当妈妈 你会当爸爸
I'm gonna be a mommy and you're gonna be a daddy!
好 各位再见 我要当妈去了
All right, I'll see you suckers. I'm gonna go get me a baby!
管他的 我要当爸去了
Oh, screw it. I'm gonna be a daddy!
菲比和谁在一起？
Hey, who's Phoebe with?
希望是"能和我上床的人"
I wanna say, "Someone I'm gonna have sex with."
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 你朋友是谁？ - 那是莎拉
- So, uh, who's your friend?     - Oh, that's Sarah.
不行 你别想打歪主意
No. Don't you get any ideas.
我不会再帮你和我朋友牵线
I'm not setting you up with any more of my friends.
- 为什么？ - 因为你只会和她约会一次
- Why? Why?     - Because you'll date her once...
和她炒饭 然后就忘了她的存在
...sleep with her, then forget she exists.
我对你哪个朋友干过这种事？
Oh! Name one friend of yours I did that with.
- 曼蒂   - 曼蒂是吗？
- Mandy.     - Mandy, huh? Uh...
金发大咪咪的尤物？
Really hot blond, big boobs?
- 不是   - 难怪我记不得
- No.     - Might be why I don't remember her, huh?
你以为我是谁啊？
Do you think I'm someone else?
我过去也许没善待你朋友
Okay, look, I may not have treated your friends well in the past.
但我成熟了 真的 对吗 瑞秋？
But I have grown up a lot. Really. Honest. Rach?
对 信不信由你 是真的
Yeah, believe it or not, it's true.
当乔伊和我约会时
I mean, when Joey and I were together...
真是一名绅士 体贴又成熟
...he was wonderful. He was thoughtful and mature.
在我们约会的一个礼拜中
And for the one week that we went out...
他完全没有偷吃
...he didn't sleep with anybody else.
这就是成长
Growth.
- 好吧 我给你她的号码    - 谢谢
- Fine, I'll give you her number.    - Okay. Thank you.
我保证不会忘记她的名字
And I promise you I will not forget this one.
- 曼蒂   - 是莎拉
- Mandy.     - Sarah!
莎拉
Sarah.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hey.    - Hi.
- 嗨   - 各位 我需要时尚顾问
- Hey.     - Hey, guys, I need some fashion advice.
啊 嗯
Oh. Huh.
这顶好看吗？
How does this look?
你…戴太低了 移高一点
Well, it's... It's a little low. Pick it up a little.
再高一点
A little bit more.
这样就对了
There you go.
现在把它丢掉
Now throw it away.
别这样 这帽子很好看
Come on! This looks good.
罗斯 相信我 我每个月读三十本时尚杂志
Ross, please trust me. I buy 30 fashion magazines a month.
我不知道谁要选总统 或北约首领是谁
Now, I don't know who's running for president or who that NATO guy is...
但我确定你要离那帽子越远越好
...but I do know that you have to get far away from that hat.
该死 老天啊…
Damn it. God...
我明晚有约会 一定要穿帅一点
I have this date tomorrow night, and I have to look cool.
若你需要行头 瑞秋和我明天要去逛街
If you want fashion help, Rachel and I are going shopping tomorrow.
- 你可以一起来   - 真的？那太好了
- You're welcome to come with us.     - Really? That would be great.
我一定要自力救济
Uh, I mean, I have to do something.
她曾经取笑过我的穿着
She kind of teased me about how I dress.
这情有可原 很帅的衬衫
I can see why. Nice shirt. Ha, ha.
你身上的是同一件
You're wearing the same shirt.
到处都是可恶的盖璞专卖店
Stupid Gap on every corner!
两位随便坐 我去带艾瑞卡来
Make yourselves comfortable, and I'll be back with Erica.
好 谢谢你
Okay, thank you.
就是这里了
Well, this is it.
- 你没事吧？ - 我很好 只是怪怪的
- Are you okay?     - Yeah, it's just weird, you know?
好像在说"我是钱德 你肚子里的人能给我吗？"
It's like, uh, "Hi, I'm Chandler. May I have the human growing inside you?"
哦
Ooh!
你会是个好爸爸
You're gonna be great.
这还用说
Well, obviously.
摩妮卡？钱德？这是艾瑞卡
Monica? Chandler? I'd like you to meet Erica.
- 嗨   - 嗨 很高兴认识你
- Hi.     - Hi. It is so, so nice to meet you.
- 嗨   - 谢谢你和我们见面
- Hi.     - Thank you for agreeing to see us.
- 嗨   - 我让你们好好聊聊
- Hi.     - I'll let you get acquainted.
- 好    - 你们是摩妮卡和钱德？
- Okay.   - So it's Monica and Chandler?
我只知道你们是 CRW 33815一D号
I only know you as "File CRW33815-D."
朋友都这么称呼我们
That's what our friends call us.
天啊  你们真是一对了不起的夫妻
Gosh, you know, you're just such an amazing couple. It's...
有点… 让我敬畏
...kind of intimidating.
这点我倒不知道
Oh, ha, ha. I don't know about that.
你在开玩笑吗？你是医生就够了不起了
Are you kidding me? I mean, it's enough that you're a doctor.
但更厉害的是你娶了位牧师？
But on top of it, you're married to a reverend?
- 这好像不是…   - 让她说完 医生
- I don't think that's exactly...     - Let her finish, doctor.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hey.
我朋友莎拉昨晚玩得很愉快
Oh, my friend Sarah had a great time last night.
- 是啊   - 那你要打电话给她吗？
- Yeah.     - Yeah, so you gonna call this one back?
不要
Ha, ha. No.
你胡说什么？莎拉人很好
What are you talking about? Sarah's great.
真的？你想知道你的 "好"朋友做了什么吗？
Oh, really? You wanna know what your "great" friend did?
我们去吃晚餐
We were out to dinner, okay?
我们很合得来 一切顺利
We were getting along, having a really nice time.
我心想她真是个酷妹
I was thinking she was really cool.
然后 天外飞来一手…
And then, out of nowhere...
就这样？
That's it?
你就为了这个原因不再约她？
That's why you won't go out with her again?
她吃了你的薯条 有什么大不了的？
So she took some fries. Big deal.
这和几根薯条无关
Hey, look, it's not about a few fries.
重点是薯条代表的意义
It's about what the fries represent.
- 什么意义？ - 所有的食物
- What?     - All food!
抱歉
Well, I'm sorry.
我竟然让你和可怕的怪物约会
I can't believe I set you up with such a monster!
听好 我请女生吃饭时
Hey, hey, hey, look, I take a girl out...
她想点什么都行 吃越多越好 懂吗？
...she can order whatever she wants. The more the better, all right?
就是不能点花园沙拉 再吃我的食物
Just don't order a garden salad and then eat my food!
很多人手指就是这样被砍断
That's a good way to lose some fingers.
真高兴你来了
Oh, thank God you're here.
- 听听看   - 怎么了？
- Listen to this.    - What?
乔伊和我朋友吃晚饭 然后她伸手
Joey and my friend are out last night, having dinner, and she reaches over...
- 拿了几根他的薯条   - 不
...and takes a few of his fries...     - Oh, no!
- 嗯   - 什么？
- Mm-hm.     - What?
你知道他爱保护食物？
You know about the plate thing?
对 乔伊不喜欢和别人分享
Oh, yeah, yeah. No, Joey doesn't share food.
上周我们共进早餐
I mean, just last week we were having breakfast...
他盘子上放了几颗葡萄
...and he had a couple grapes on his plate.
- 你不让她吃葡萄？ - 不是我
- You wouldn't let her have a grape?     - Oh, no, not me.
是艾玛
Emma.
乔伊不和人分享食物
Joey doesn't share food!
我还是觉得这是拒绝往来的烂理由
Well, I still think that is a stupid reason not to call someone again.
你非得打给她 知道吗？
You are calling her, okay?
有必要的话就多点一盘薯条
And if you need to, then just get an extra plate of fries for the table.
好主意
I like that.
缓冲用薯条 没错
A sharing buffer. Yeah.
好 我多点一盘薯条 或一盘洋葱圈
Yeah, I'll order some extra fries. Maybe a plate of onion rings.
真是妙招
Yeah. Yeah.
还有鲜虾盅
And a shrimp cocktail.
再来点水牛城鸡翅
Uh-huh. And some Buffalo wings.
或者…再来个一人份披萨？
Maybe... Maybe an individual pizza, huh?
还有黄金起士条
And some mozzarella sticks.
我们怎么在讲这个？
What were we talking about?
这里真好逛
Wow, this place is awesome.
我们走吧 这里没有适合我穿的
We should just go. I'm not gonna find anything here.
这玩意儿怎么见人？
This stuff is ridiculous.
这真是购物天堂
Oh, this place is great!
哇哦
Wow.
瑞秋 我不要穿这些 我讨厌银色
Rach, come on, I'm not gonna wear any of this. Nothing silver.
- 为什么？ - 我也不要有毛的
- Wha...?     - Okay, nothing with hair.
- 有锁的也不行   - 啊
- And nothing with padlocks on it!     - Aw.
罗斯 我知道有些衣服很俗气
Ross, look. Look, I know that some of this stuff is out there.
但是你看看这件毛衣
But, I mean, come on, look at this. Look at this sweater.
实在太好看了
I mean, this is just beautiful.
好柔软喔
Wow, this is really soft.
三百五十块？
Three hundred and fifty dollars?
原价要七百 你省了两百块左右
Down from 700. You're saving like 200 bucks.
今天大家的逻辑和数学都不太好
Both logic and math are taking a serious hit today.
看看这件 完全是你的风格
Hey, check this out. It's totally you.
- 哇   - 是啊
- Wow.     - Yeah.
哈
Huh.
这件的确很适合我
Wow. Actually, this looks pretty good.
- 是啊   - 是啊
- Yeah.     - Yeah.
"长不大的男孩？"
"Boys will be boys"?
- 什么？本来就是   - 对
- What? They will be!    - All right.
- 够了 我要走了   - 不 罗斯你等等
- That's it, I'm getting out of here.    - No, Ross, wait, come on.
还有别的选择 看这些帅气的衬衫和长裤
There's other stuff here. There's some nice shirts, these nice pants.
其实这些应该蛮适合我的
Huh. Actually, these might look pretty good on me.
没错 你知道该怎么做吗？去散步
Yes, they will. You know what you should do? Go take a walk.
好吗？我知道你的尺寸 我帮你桃些好货色
I know your size, and I'm gonna pick out some really good stuff for you.
- 真的？ - 对
- Really?     - Yes.
我知道男人穿什么最性感
I know what looks sexy on guys.
穿我帮你挑的衣服 她就会为你疯狂
Just wear what I suggest, and she is gonna go nuts for you.
所以你的意思是…
So you're saying, uh...
若我穿这条长裤 就能脱掉她的？
...if I wear these pants, I might be getting into hers?
男人怎么老是这样说话？
Why do men keep talking to me like this?
我是医生 我妻子是牧师…
So the fact that I'm a doctor and my wife's a reverend...
这点对你很重要吗？
...that's important to you?
对 我看过很多优秀的申请人
Yeah. I read some great applications...
但我想 "谁比牧师更适合抚养小孩？"
...but I thought, "Who better than a minister to raise a child?"
阿门
Amen.
我也认为孩子由医生照顾再好不过
Plus, I thought the baby would be in good hands with a doctor.
灵活的双手
Oh, good hands.
有治疗魔法的双手
Healing hands.
牧师 请问圣经对收养有何着墨？
Reverend, can I ask? Does the Bible say anything about adoption?
圣经说"做就对了"
It says, "Do it."
"看 她的确将孩子给他们收养"
"And behold, she did adopt unto them a baby.
"很好的决定"
And it was good."
- 哇   - 是啊 哇
- Wow.     - Yeah, wow.
我在想你们两位工作如此繁重
I was wondering... You both have such serious jobs.
会有时间同时照顾孩子和教徒吗？
Would you have time to take care of a baby and your flock?
不 我的教徒？他们都很好
Oh, no, my flock? My flock is good.
对 他们现在都会照顾自己了
Yeah. My flock pretty much takes care of themselves by this point.
很乖的教徒 教徒
It's a good flock. Flock, flock, flock.
但是当医生一定很忙
But being a doctor, that must take up a lot of time.
我不会忙
Not for me it doesn't.
谈得如何？
So how's everything going in here?
很好 该问的问题我都问了
We're great. I think I may have asked all my questions.
很好 你们有问题要问艾瑞卡吗？
Good. Do you have questions for Erica?
有 你看到一份你中意的档案
Yeah, actually. So you read a file that you liked...
然后就给这单位序号 他们就联络我们？
...and then you gave the agency the serial number and they contacted us?
对 本系统保证完全匿名
Oh, yes. Our system ensures total anonymity.
- 我们深感为仿   - 应该的
- We're very proud of it.     - You should be.
你们的一切都很完善
You're really on top of stuff.
若没有其他问题 我俩应该谈谈
Well, then if there's nothing else, then the two of us should talk.
其实…
I actually...
- 我们不用谈了   - 不用？
- I don't think we have to.     - We don't?
对 我看到你们的档案时 就确定要选你们…
Yeah, when I read about you two, I was pretty sure I wanted you...
但我想还是亲自见面比较好
...but I just thought we should meet face to face.
我已经决定了
I've made my decision.
我选他们
I choose them. Heh.
天啊 太好了
Oh, my God, this is great.
太棒了 你听到了吗？
This is so great. Did you hear that?
我听到了
Yeah, I did.
好的
Okay.
- 谢谢 真的很感谢你   - 哈哈
- Thank you. Thank you so much. Oh.     - Ha, ha.
你一定会上天堂
Oh. You are so going to heaven!
- 我们买了很多好东西   - 对
- Oh, we got some really great stuff.     - Yeah.
但我不确定那些内衣合不合身
Yeah, but I'm not sure about some of the bras I got.
真的？你要试穿给我看吗？
Oh, really? Do you wanna try some of them on for me?
好
Oh, okay.
等等 我们是乔伊的幻想吗？
Wait, are we in Joey's imagination?
糟糕 我不小心拿到罗斯的袋子了
Oh, no. I took one of Ross' bags by mistake.
我的一袋也不见了
And one of mine is missing.
可能在罗斯那里 待会找他拿就好了
Ross probably has it. You'll get it from him later.
你觉得如何？
So, what do you think?
我们没穿同一件上衣了
I think we're not wearing the same shirt anymore.
对 瑞秋帮我挑的
Yeah. Yeah, Rachel picked it out for me.
她要我相信她 你知道吗？ 还好我听她的
She told me to trust her, and you know what? I'm glad I did.
一路上很多人都回头看我
I turned quite a few heads on my way over here.
老兄 我真的认为你不该穿这件
Dude, I really don't think you should be wearing that.
我懂了
Oh, I see.
有人担心泡妞时出现对手？
Somebody's afraid of a little competition with the ladies?
似乎有人自己就是小妞
Looks like someone is the ladies!
你只是忌妒 因为你比不上我
You're just jealous because you couldn't pull this off.
抱歉失陪了 我要去约会
Yeah. Now if you'll excuse me, I have a date.
看到没？我是目光的焦点
See? All eyes on me!
- 我们不能签收养文件   - 为什么？
- We are not signing those papers.     - Why not?
这是不对的 他们把我们当成别人了
It's wrong. They made a mistake. They think we're somebody else.
上帝的旨意总是变幻莫测
God works in mysterious ways.
你得停下来了
You have gotta stop.
但她很喜欢我们
But she liked us.
她喜欢的是钱德医生 和摩妮卡牧师
She likes Doctor Chandler and Reverend Monica.
若你仔细想想 我也算是牧师
If you think about it, I'm kind of like a reverend.
身为厨师 我借由喂食饥民与穷人服侍上帝
I mean, as a chef, I serve God by feeding the hungry and poor.
你的小牛排要三十五块美金
Your veal chop is 34.95.
拜托 我只是… 我认为这是个机会
Come on, I just... I think we've been given an opportunity.
反正错都已经犯了 他们已经在拟合约了
The mistake's already made. They're writing up the papers now.
但她选的不是我们
But we're not the ones she chose.
你怎么能够心安？
How can you feel okay about this?
因为…
Because.
我们也许不是她心里的人选
We may not be who she thinks we are...
但没人会比我们更爱这个孩子
...but no one will ever love that baby more than us.
- 我知道   - 我是说谁知道…
- I know.     - I mean, who knows...
去收养另一个小孩还要等多久？
...how long it's gonna take for someone else to give us a baby?
万一永远没人选我们呢？
What if no one ever picks us?
宝贝…
Oh, honey...
求求你？
Please?
拜托 就差这临门一脚
Please. We are so close.
摩妮卡 我也想要孩子
Monica, I want a baby too.
但这女人要把孩子送人
But this woman is giving away her child.
她有权利知道收养人到底是谁
She deserves to know who it's going to.
好 你说得没错
Okay. You're right.
我们去告诉她真相
So we'll tell the truth.
谁知道？也许她会喜欢真正的我们
And who knows, you know? Maybe she'll like us for us.
也许她会
Maybe she will.
为什么我不是牧师？
Oh, why couldn't I have been a reverend?
你是犹太人
You're Jewish.
真吹毛求疵
Technicality!
小姐的花园沙拉
Garden salad for the lady.
- 很好吃的感觉 点得好   - 哈哈
- Oh, that looks great. Good ordering.     -  Ha-ha-ha.
先生的海鲜拼盘和加点的薯条
Seafood platter for the gentleman, and extra fries.
- 请享用  - 哈哈
- Enjoy. - Ha, ha.
这些着条看来真好吃
Mm. Those fries look delicious.
- 我不知道你喜欢吃薯条    - 哈哈
- Oh, I didn't know you liked french fries.     - Ha, ha.
你尽量吃 我的就是你的
Help yourself. What's mine is yours.
那些是镶蛤蜊吗？
Oh. Wow, are those stuffed clams?
额
Uh...
对 是我的镶蛤蜊
Yes, they are my stuffed clams.
这些薯条好不好吃？
How about those fries, though, huh?
- 很好吃   - 对
- They are delicious. Ha-ha-ha.     - Yeah.
你知道你很美吗？
You are beautiful, you know that?
你嘴真甜
That is so sweet.
那就好
Okay, then.
嗯
Mm.
Mm-hm.
看你干的好事
Now look what you did!
什么？你有什么毛病？
What? What is the matter with you?
我不喜欢别人吃我 盘子上的东西 行吗？
I don't like it when people take food off of my plate, okay?
你刚不是说"我的就是你的"
But you said, "What's mine is yours."
我是乱讲的
Well, I didn't mean it!
真抱歉 我没想到有这么严重
Fine. Sorry, I didn't think it was that big a deal.
不是 抱歉 我…
No, I'm sorry. I...
我反应过度了 只是关于食物…
I'm overreacting, okay? It's just, when it comes to food, I...
我有一些坚持
...have certain rules...
你懂吗？我是说…
...okay? I mean...
有些事能做 有些事不能做
...there are things you do, and, you know, things that you don't do.
这里真漂亮
Wow, this place looks great.
你一定会喜欢 真高兴我俩终于能来
Oh, you are gonna love it. And I'm so glad we're finally doing this.
- 我也是   - 我帮你
- Me too.     - Here.
今晚真好玩
So this was fun.
刚刚的事我很抱歉
I really am sorry about, you know, before.
希望你了解我真的很喜欢你
And I wanna make sure you know I really do like you.
当然 只是你更爱蛤蜊
Sure, just not as much as clams.
是镶蛤蜊
Well, stuffed clams, ha, ha...
- 小姐的巧克力果仁蛋糕    - 嗯
- Chocolate torte for the lady.     - Mm.
先生的起士蛋糕
Cheesecake for the gentleman.
抱歉 我的蛋糕上 好像有红红的怪东西
Uh, excuse me, sir. There seems to be some sort of red crap on my cheesecake.
没错 那是桑堪水果酱
Oh. Yes, that's a raspberry coulis.
白痴才会点起士蛋糕 我只想吃得健康
I'm so stupid ordering cheesecake, trying to be healthy.
真好吃
Oh, my God. Mm.
- 我来一份她点的好了   - 抱歉 先生
- I'll just have what she's having.     - I'm sorry, sir.
-  那是最后一片   - 额
- That was our last piece.     - Mm.
嗯 嗯
Mm. Mm.
哦 不
Oh, no.
公司打来的 我得回电 失陪一下好吗？
This is work. I should call in. Can you excuse me?
当然 没问题
Oh, yeah, sure. No problem.
你干什么？你不是讨厌分享食物？
What are you doing? I thought you don't share food?
没错
Sure I do.
- 水果酱？ - 哈哈
- Coulis? - Ha, ha.
不 我不能吃你的蛤蜊 你也别想碰我的甜点
No. If I can't have your clams, you can't have my dessert.
我们要礼尚往来
This is a two-way street.
真的？
Really?
真的
Really.
等我回来蛋糕最好还在桌上
Now this all better be here when I come back.
当然 我有自制力
Yeah, of course. I can control myself. Ha-ha-ha. Yeah.
不要盯着我看
Stop staring at me!
一点点就好…
Just a tiny little... Ha, ha.
额
Uh-oh.
我甚至问心无愧
I'm not even sorry.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.    - Hey.
这是公开收养的初期表格
So these are the preliminary forms for an open adoption. Uh...
内容很繁复 但我会一一解释
There's a lot to go over, but I'll explain as we go through.
- 那是照片吗？ - 对
- Is that a picture?     - Yeah.
上周宝宝的超音波扫描图
It's a sonogram they took of the baby last week.
你们应该会想看
I thought you might wanna see it.
你看 医生
Look, doctor.
在签名之前 我们要和你谈谈
Look, before we sign anything, we really have to talk.
我们不是你认为的那对夫妻
We're not who you think we are.
- 我不了解   - 认养机关一定搞错了
- I don't understand.    - The agency must have made a mistake.
我妻子不是牧师 我也不是医生
My wife is not a reverend, and I'm not a doctor.
- 什么？ - 这不可能
- What?   - That's impossible.
你愿意的话我能帮你问问
I could perform an operation on you and prove it if you'd like.
我去检查你们的档案 失陪
Um, I have to check your file. Excuse me.
那你们是谁？
So who are you?
我们的真名是摩妮卡和钱德 来自纽约
Our names really are Monica and Chandler. We're from New York.
对 但最重要的是…
Yeah, but the important thing to know about us...
我们多渴望这个小宝宝
...is how much we would care for this little baby.
所以你们之前骗我？
So you lied to me before?
我们"见证这个错误"
Well, we "bore false witness."
听到没？我也能当牧师
See? I could be a reverend.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
但我们希望既然说了实话
But we were hoping that since we told you the truth...
你依旧会考虑…   - 把宝宝给你们？
...that you still might consider...     - Giving you my baby?
你们认为我会把孩子交给骗子？
You think I'd give you my child after this?
你不用现在决定 若你看我们的档案…
You don't have to decide now. If you look at our file...
我不要看 这件事到此为止
I don't wanna look at your file. This is over.
艾瑞卡 等等
Erica, wait.
我们没什么好谈的
I have nothing to say to you.
你非常有资格生气 我们是说谎没错
Look, you have every reason to be upset. We did lie.
但这是因为我们盼孩子盼了好久
But only because we've been waiting and trying to have a baby for so long.
也不知道下一个机会何时才会来临
And we don't know how long it's gonna be before we get another chance.
你何不请那牧师祷告？
Why don't you ask the reverend to pray on it?
艾瑞卡 拜托你
Erica, please.
请考虑我们 请他们让你看我们的档案
Just consider us. Ask them to see our file.
我们姓宾
Our last name's Bing.
我妻子是厨师 我是广告人
My wife's a chef and I'm in advertising.
对了
Oh, yeah.
我其实很喜欢你们
I actually liked you guys.
但那不重要 你们的行为是错的
But it doesn't matter. What you did was wrong.
但你的确喜欢我们
But you did like us.
我们也很值得
And you should.
我妻子是个了不起的女人
My wife's an incredible woman.
她细心 热情又体贴
She is loving, and devoted and caring.
别说是我说的 但那女人永远是对的
And don't tell her I said this, but the woman's always right.
我爱我妻子胜于一切
I love my wife more than anything in this world.
万一…
And it...
万一我无法给她孩子 我会心碎
It kills me that I can't give her a baby.
我真的很想要小孩
I really want a kid.
有了孩子后 我会学习当个好爸爸
And when that day finally comes, I'll learn how to be a good dad.
但我妻子…
But my wife...
她已经准备好了
...she's already there.
她是个好母亲…
She's a mother...
只差孩子的到来
...without a baby.
求求你？
Please?
你还想要那个孩子吗？
You still want that baby?
上帝保佑你 钱德宾
God bless you, Chandler Bing!
原来那件毛衣是女人穿的
Turns out this sweater is made for a woman.
那你干嘛还穿着？
So why are you still wearing it?
因为很柔软
Because it's soft.
- 你的约会还顺利吗？ - 额
- Hey, so how was your date?     - Ugh.
不太好
Not so good.
今晚好像就我俩共度 老兄
Well, looks like it's just the two of us tonight, huh, buddy?
对 你知道吗？其实还不算糟
Yeah. And you know what? We could do a lot worse.
- 没错   - 没错
- Yeah.     - Yeah. Ha-ha-ha.
乔伊不和人分享食物
Joey doesn't share food!